Lesson 23. Bob has a surprise visitor. Bob's former boss Peter from the furniture store
comes to visit. He offers Bob his old job back, but Bob's not interested.
Hi Bob, I was just in the neighborhood so I thought I'd stop by.
Come on in. Take a cookie. Thanks. I'm glad to see you're not holding a
wedge against me for firing you. Not at all. At first it burned me up, but I feel
better. Good. I'm glad you have no hard feelings. How would you like your old
job back? What happened to your wonderful new manager? She drank the twerk. By
five o'clock she'd be lying under a dining room table. Three seats to the wind.
Yesterday I finally got rid of her. Let me get this straight. You replaced me with
some crazy woman who got plastered every day on the job. Yes, I lost my head.
I don't think you lost your head. I just think you've got rocks in your head.
Bob, I'm trying to level with you. I never should have let you go. No use crying
over spilt milk. So you'll come back and work for me? Not in your life. Susan and I
are very well off now. We just sold our new company for a small fortune.